Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Once upon a time, in a certain place...
Prehistoric creatures full of personality!
Tirano, Stego, Ammonite,Trilobite.
They've been saying "hi" for 500 million years.
Prehistory! Everybody Say (Roar!)
Ancient, Alright! Future, FLY High!
A herd of mammoths! Run!
Thud thud thud thud! On your marks, get set, go!
Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Dive deep into serious learning,
Playing for real.
The universe begins with passion.
Super happy!
Serious Dunkleosteus Comedy Contest
Hmm,
what should I do?
What is that?
We have a live show with the Idol Club,
but I can't decide on an outfit.
Look at those cute frills.
Frills?
That might actually work!
Eww, wait! What is that?!
This is a Triceratops skull!
This one is a juvenile,
but adults are much bigger!
So let's jump...
into the WORLD OF SERIOUS PALEONTOLOGY!
Hey, I'm not going!
Whoa!
This is an adult Triceratops!
Its name means "three-horned face"!
It features a short horn on its nose and
two long ones on its brow,
totaling three horns!
The horns look different between juveniles and adults, right?
And another thing!
The neck crest!
this frill is also a major feature of Triceratops!
Why do they have frills?
It was used by males to show off to females!
To show off?
And then,
T-Tyrannosaurus!
The frill also protected their vital neck from carnivorous dinosaurs!
Amazing!
Furthermore...
Triceratops skulls are extremely hard!
Dinosaurs with frills and face horns are called Ceratopsians!
Are there any other kinds?
Look at this!
Pachyrhinosaurus!
It has hair all over its body?!
That's right!
It also has large bony bosses above its eyes and nose!
Theories suggest males used them in fights
or to attract females!
So it was for showing off after all.
Also,
if other ceratopsians broke a horn, it stayed broken,
but Pachyrhinosaurus might have been able to regenerate them!
Just like a lizard's tail!
And look...
There are holes in the frill!
There are many other ceratopsians as well!
This is Chasmosaurus!
Its frill might have had eye-like patterns to intimidate enemies!
What?!
You look like a frog paralyzed by a snake!
And over here is Styracosaurus!
A ceratopsian with a total of seven sharp spikes!
Spikes?!
Come on,
Ceratopsians!
So frills came in all sorts of varieties.
Indeed!
There were many dinosaurs with frills.
However,
Triceratops skulls were especially solid,
which is why so many of their fossils survive to this day!
I get it.
To survive as an idol, you need toughness,
a rock-solid resolve to succeed!
Tetori is using Triceratops to teach me that!
Kanna-kun,
I bestow this upon you.
You can do it!
Become an idol like a Triceratops!
A Tricera-idol?
Time to show off!
LIKE I EVER COULD!